You've only heard the cold, cold beat A rhythm
made of steel But this is what we listen to This is
what we feel
It's electric It's alive, you can dance to this
all night It's not the dark, it's not the grey
It's all electric calibrate You've only heard
the single note The whisper and the drone But
this is for the stadium You'll never be alone
So raise your hands and shout it out. This is the
sound we share. We are the sound. We are the
crowd. And we are everywhere.
This is your 80s education A brand new, better
protocol This is the sound of your salvation A
mixtape here to break your fall It's not the beat
of her machine It's the music in between
My mother's sound was like a thicket cage A cold
and empty room But this is like a different age A
flower in full bloom I've never heard this much
joy I've never felt this free Is this what I was
missing? Is this all for me?
It's all for you The high, the low The sappy songs
that make you cry The harbor in the storm, you
know The soundtrack for your brand new sky
This is your 80's education A brand new, better
protocol This is the sound of your salvation A
mixtape here to break your fall It's not the beat
of a machine It's the music in between
Welcome to the 80s, Jordan. We have a lot to
cover.